Henry Smith Munroe Papers
Connecticut Historical Society
- V. Financial Papers
  - Receipts and bills of sale (2)., [188-]-[189-] (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Insurance Papers., 1889-1916 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Indentures and agreements., 1886-1893 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- VI. Columbia University
  - Lecture notes for Mining 81 and 91., 1909 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Lecture notes for Mining 56., 1910 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Columbia School of Mines and Summer School of Mining: Student information, grade schedules, class sheets and society information., 1887-1911 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- VII. Barrell Lands
  - Barrell Lands: Undated notes and memoranda., [187-]-[19--] (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Barrell Lands: Undated notes and memoranda., [187-]-[19--] (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Barrell Lands Survey by J. W. Davis (Office Book no. 3), [188-] (Box 12)
  - Trustees of the Barrell Lands: Minutes., 1886-1888 (Box 12)
- VIII. St. Lawrence Pyrites Company: Financial Statements
  - St. Lawrence Pyrites Company: financial statements., 1906-1907 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - St. Lawrence Pyrites Company: contracts and production statistics., 1908 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - St. Lawrence Pyrites Company: financial statements., 1908 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - St. Lawrence Pyrites Company: financial statements., 1909 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- IX. Maps, Plans and Engineering Diagrams
  - Maps, plans and engineering diagrams (1)., [19-?] (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Maps, plans and engineering diagrams (2). Includes photograph of aluminum drainage pipe., [19-?] (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Maps, plans and engineering diagrams (3). Plans relate to land in Grundy County, TN., [183-/] (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Maps, plans and engineering diagrams (4). Plans relate to land around DeKalb, and Grundy County, TN, and Litchfield, CT., 1898-[19-?] (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Maps, plans and blue-prints relating to the Anna mine., 1908-1910 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Surveys of Litchfield, CT., 1884-1887 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Engineering notes prepared by Juan Webster [?] relating to the Ouro mine, Bolivia., 1884-1887 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Undated engineering notes and jottings., [18-?] - [19-?] (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Undated engineering notes and jottings., [18-] - [19-] (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Series 10: Memorabilia
- X. Memorabilia
  - Invitations, business cards, menus, and tickets., [19-] (Box 13, Folder 10)
- XI. Whitney Estate
  - Whitney estate., 1886-1889 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- XII. Felix Grundy Mining Co.
  - Grundy Mining Company: Minutes., 1879-1880 (Volume 5)
  - Grundy Mining Company: Minutes., 1882-1884 (Volume 6)